let questions = [
    {
        question: 'Which conjunction can you use to join two similar ideas?',
        choices: ['and', 'but', 'or', 'either'],
        correctAnswer: 'a',
        word: 'and',
        definition: '"And" is a conjunction used to join two similar ideas. Example: I like to read books and watch movies.'
    },
    {
        question: 'I want to go to the park, ___ its raining outside.',
        choices: ['but', 'and', 'or', 'so'],
        correctAnswer: 'a',
        word: 'but',
        definition: '"But" is a conjunction used to show contrast between two ideas. Example: I want to go to the park, but its raining outside.'
    },
    {
        question: 'She studied hard _____ she passed the exam.',
        choices: ['so', 'because', 'if', 'but'],
        correctAnswer: 'a',
        word: 'so',
        definition: '"So" is a conjunction used to indicate a reason or cause. Example: She studied hard, so she passed the exam.'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which conjunction can you use to show contrast between two ideas?',
        choices: ['and', 'but', 'or', 'else'],
        correctAnswer: 'b',
        word: 'but',
        definition: '"But" is a conjunction used to show contrast between two ideas. Example: I like both chocolate but vanilla ice cream.'
    },
    {
        question: 'I like both chocolate ___ vanilla ice cream.',
        choices: ['and', 'or', 'but', 'just'],
        correctAnswer: 'a',
        word: 'and',
        definition: '"And" is a conjunction used to join two similar ideas. Example: I like both chocolate and vanilla ice cream.'
    },
    {
        question: 'We can go out for dinner now ____  later.',
        choices: ['or ', 'yet', 'but', 'all of the above'],
        correctAnswer: 'a',
        word: 'or',
        definition: '"or" is a conjunction used to  Connects two or more possibilities or alternatives.'
    },
    {
        question: 'John can\'t speak Japanese, ____ he can speak Spanish.',
        choices: ['so', 'nor', 'but', 'all of the above'],
        correctAnswer: 'c',
        word: 'but',
        definition: '"but" is a conjunction Used to indicate contrast or opposition between elements in a sentence.'
    },
    {
        question: 'I was late, _____ I decided to take a taxi to work.',
        choices: ['for ', 'yet', 'so', 'all of the above'],
        correctAnswer: 'c',
        word: 'so',
        definition: '"so" is a conjunction used to introduce clauses of result or decision.'
    },
    {
        question: 'My classmate didn\'t study for the test,_____ she still passed.',
        choices: [' yet ', 'nor', ' or', 'all of the above'],
        correctAnswer: 'a',
        word: 'yet',
        definition: '"yet" is  The conjunction “yet” is used in a  sentence if you want to let others know that you are still in a situation and it is going to continue in the near future '
    },
    {
        question: ' In the end, the company didn\'t make money... did it lose money.',
        choices: ['for ', ' nor', 'so', 'all of the above'],
        correctAnswer: 'b',
        word: 'nor',
        definition: '"so" Use the conjunction “nor” before the second of farther of two alternatives when “neither” introduces the first.'
    },
    {
        question: 'My pet cat is cold and hungry... it didn\'t come back home last night.',
        choices: ['for ', 'or', 'nor', 'all of the above'],
        correctAnswer: 'a',
        word: 'for',
        definition: 'The conjunction “For” has multiple uses; it can function as a coordinating conjunction, to connect words or groups of words together,  but it can also function as a preposition '
    },
    {
        question: 'Seoul is a large city, ____ it is located in Asia.',
        choices: ['but  ', ' and', 'so', 'all of the above'],
        correctAnswer: 'b',
        word: 'and',
        definition: 'To connect two words, phrases, clauses, or prefixes together and Use the conjunction “and” to connect grammatically coordinate words, phrases, or clauses '
    },
    {
        question: 'The universe is a big place,... there may be intelligent life out there.',
        choices: ['or ', ' for', 'so', 'all of the above'],
        correctAnswer: 'b',
        word: 'for',
        definition: 'To talk about a purpose or a reason for something and The conjunction “For” has multiple uses; it can function as a coordinating conjunction, to connect words or groups of words together,  but it can also function as a preposition '
    },
    {
        question: 'I have some free time _____ an extra ticket. Do you want to see a movie?',
        choices: ['and ', 'for', 'yet', 'all of the above'],
        correctAnswer: 'a',
        word: 'and',
        definition: 'To connect two words, phrases, clauses, or prefixes together and  Use the conjunction “and” to connect grammatically coordinate words, phrases, or clauses '
    },
    {
        question: ' I'+'m not really hungry, _____ that apple pie looks delicious!',
        choices: ['so ', 'yet', 'nor', 'all of the above'],
        correctAnswer: 'b',
        word: 'yet',
        definition: 'We use “yet” as an adverb to refer to a time which starts in the past and continues up to the present and The conjunction “yet” is used in a  sentence if you want to let others know that you are still in a situation and it is going to continue in the near future '
    },
    {
        question: 'Elephants are big, but blue whales are even bigger.',
        choices: ['blue ', 'big', 'but', 'all of the above'],
        correctAnswer: 'c',
        word: 'but',
        definition: 'Conjunction “but” means “on the contrary” and Used to indicate contrast or opposition between elements in a sentence.'
    },
    {
        question: 'The capital city of the United States is not New York, nor is it Los Angeles.',
        choices: ['The ', ' nor', ' city', 'all of the above'],
        correctAnswer: 'b',
        word: 'nor',
        definition: 'Introduce a second negative clause and Use the conjunction “nor” before the second of farther of two alternatives when “neither” introduces the first.'
    },
    {
        question: 'Can you help me carry these books, or are you busy right now?',
        choices: ['help ', 'are', ' or', 'all of the above'],
        correctAnswer: 'c',
        word: 'or',
        definition: ' Connects two or more possibilities or alternatives'
    },
    {
        question: 'I need a pen and some paper to write some notes.',
        choices: ['and', 'a', ' I', 'all of the above'],
        correctAnswer: 'a',
        word: 'and',
        definition: 'To connect two words, phrases, clauses, or prefixes together and  Use the conjunction “and” to connect grammatically coordinate words, phrases, or clauses'
    },
    {
        question: 'Sam lived in France for two years, so he can speak French.',
        choices: ['so', 'lived', 'can', 'all of the above'],
        correctAnswer: 'a',
        word: 'so',
        definition: 'The conjunction “so” is used to introduce clauses of result or decision'
    }
]

export default questions;